<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Website</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 17:41:56 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Whist Tournaments for Euchre</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whist-tournament-maker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 17:41:56 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whist-tournament-maker/</guid>
      <description>My dad has a friend that holds an annual Euchre tournament each year on St. Patties day. It&amp;rsquo;s a pretty big deal, anywhere from 20-30 people will show up to see who takes home a non-trivial cash prize. The format is unique and very similar to a round-robin style tournament, but with a twist. Each round the teams are randomly chosen via each person pulling a piece of paper out of a hat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuing my education</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/continuing-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:32:34 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/continuing-education/</guid>
      <description>Edit - July 15th, 2024: After about a month of attempting this system I am putting it on pause. There are a few problems I have encountered thus far:&#xA;Despite setting a goal of 7 hours per week, I have not put in place a real system to achieve this goal. 7 hours per week is difficult to achieve during weeks of extended work or vacation, the system does not account for this.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/initial-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 12:03:10 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/initial-post/</guid>
      <description>This is the first ever post for the third iteration of my personal website that now features blogging thanks to the excellent Hugo static site generator. In this post I want to explain my thoughts about what should go on the site, touch on some of the technologies used to build the site, and briefly discuss my thoughts on the look of the site.&#xA;What should go on the website? The software engineer/developer portfolio websites I have seen usually look similar to a resume, with sections such as &amp;ldquo;work experience&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;education&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;skills&amp;rdquo;, etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Directory</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/directory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/directory/</guid>
      <description>A digital garden of links to interesting or frequently visited places.&#xA;Project Showcase Whist Tournament Maker Blogs Eli Bendersky Michael Lynch Scott Galloway Soham Kanami Spotify Strava Garmin Proton Resources University of Michigan EECS Course Guide University of Michigan Open Courseware MIT Open Courseware learnxinyminutes.com Math Explainers Golang Examples Beej&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Network Programming Competitive Programming Algorithms Learning Synthesizers Google Style Guides Open Source Iconography Read the Docs Golang Angular Web Docs Models Circuits Applet Finate State Machine Designer Turing Machine Regex Generator News Hacker News Wired Ars Technica TechCrunch IEEE Spectrum Reference FCC Frequency Allocation Spectrum (2016) </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
